

CONTACT

- **Q** 09361800144
- pengaaaaay01@gmail.com
- 1727 Escuela St., Guadalupe Nuevo Makati City

EDUCATION

2016-2018 PITOGO SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

2018-2022 UNIVERSITY OF MAKATI

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Baking
- Cooking
- Bartending
- Housekeeping

SKILLS

- Detail Oriented
- Time Management
- Effective Communication
- Problem Solver
- Fast Learner

CERTIFICATION

- NC II Cookery
- NC II Housekeeping
- · NC II Bartending

LORREYNE

CRISTOBAL

PROFILE

A 25 years old graduate student of Bachelor of Science in Hospitality Management, aiming for a role in a well-respected organization, with a challenging opportunity where I can utilize and improve my skills, enable me to gain more experience and knowledge, and allow me to grow personally and professionally.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Watami Grill and Sushi Bar

January 2023 - September 2024

Sever and Bartender

· Handling guests at the bar, clearing and setting tables, serving food, handling cash and serving alcohol, stocking and cleaning the bar, and coordinating guest requests are the primary functions of the job.

Texas RoadHouse

August 2022 - November 2022

Server

- · Food and beverage serving and related workers are the front line of customer service in restaurants and other food service establishments.
- · They seat customers, take or prepare food and drink orders, clear and set tables and serve food and beverages.

Tesda Womens Center

March 2022 - June 2022

Bartending

 Bartenders must have a strong understanding of mixology techniques, cocktail recipes, and flavor combination.

REFERENCE

Shella Bawar

Maria Encaarnacion Rojo

Michael Tawingan

Tesda Trainer

General Manager

Sofitel Cost Control Manager

Phone: 0925-842-0911

Phone: 0977-033-5135

Phone: 0919-022-5614